hello.
こんにちわ
You're so cute.
あなちゃん、かわいいね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいです
Are you nervous?
緊張してる?
I'm nervous.
緊張してます
I will.
するよね
I'm going to do something naughty now.
今からエッチなことするけど
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいね
What do you usually do?
普段何してるの?
I usually go to a vocational school.
普段は専門学校に通ってます
That's right.
そうなんだ
What vocational school?
何の専門学校?
This is the nursing department.
看護科です
Oh, you went to nursing?
あ、看護科行ってんだ?
Is it quite difficult?
結構大変?
It's tough, isn't it?
大変ですね
Will I become a nurse after I graduate?
卒業したら看護師になるのかな?
I will become a nurse.
看護師になります
You can see a lot of naughty things about nurses.
看護師さんのエッチなところいっぱい見れるね
You look like a great idol.
すごいアイドルみたいな顔してるね
You can have it, right?
持てるでしょ?
I can't have it at all.
全然持てないです
What kind of man do you like?
どういう男の人が好きなの?
I want someone who is kind and naughty.
優しくて、エッチな人がいいです
I like naughty people.
エッチな人がいいんだ
That's right.
そうなんだ
why?
なんで?
Is it bad for men who don't have sexual desire?
性欲がない男の人ダメ?
That's no good.
ダメですね
What if I have a boyfriend?
彼氏いたら何?
Did you have sex every day?
毎日エッチした?
I want to do it every day.
毎日したいです
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
What kind of professional are you?
どういうプロじゃん?
That's great.
最高だね
He's an active person.
積極的な人だね
She looks like Mako Akimoto from Nogizaka, right?
乃木坂の秋元真子ちゃんに似てるよね?
It is said.
言われます
That's amazing.
すごいな
Please wear cute clothes.
服も可愛いの着ててね
When was the last time you had sex?
最近はいつエッチしたの?
The latest was a week ago.
最近は一週間前です
That's right.
そうなんだ
how was it?
どうだった?
That sex.
そのエッチは
It burned.
燃 えました
Did it burn?
燃えました?
Was he handsome?
イケメンだった?
yes.
はい
Oh, he was handsome.
あ、イケメンだったんだ
It looks funny, just the face.
面食いそうだもんね、顔がね
That's not the case.
そんなことないです
Ah, yes.
あ、そう
Can I go with my uncle?
おじさんとかもいけるの?
it's okay.
大丈夫です
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
The strike zone is pretty wide.
ストライクゾーン広いね、結構ね
yes.
はい
What kind of sex do you like?
どういうエッチが好きなの?
What kind of sex?
どういうエッチ?
But I like being kind.
でも優しいのが好きです
Ah, I like sex that has an atmosphere.
あ、雰囲気があるようなエッチが好きなんだ
But Kuro-chan will probably bully you.
でも黒ちゃんたぶんいじめちゃうよ
I like that too.
そういうのも好きです
Oh, I like that too.
あ、そういうのも好きなんだ
That's amazing.
すごいね
You have quite a strong sexual desire.
結構性欲強いね
Then.
そ したらね
How many people have you had sex with so far?
今まで何人くらいとエッチしたことあるの?
Until now, there are only three people.
今までは3人くらいです
Oh, there's only about 3 people?
あ、3人くらいしかいないんだ?
So what did you do a month ago?
じゃあ1ヶ月前にやったのは?
Was it a week ago?
1週間前だっけ?
The one I did a week ago was the third one?
1週間前にやったのは3人目だったこと?
yes.
はい
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
Shouldn't it be commemorated?
記念すべきじゃない?
Commemorative.
記念すべき
Ah, yes.
あ、そう
That's right.
そっかそっか
Don't you ever date?
付き合ったりはしないの?
I agree.
そうですね
I'm not thinking about it right now.
今は考えてない
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
Was it a one night love?
ワンナイトラブだったの?
It was one night.
ワンナイトでした
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
Wherever I go, I see something cute like this,
どこに行ったらこんな可愛いこと、
I guess we can do it for one night.
ワンナイトできるんだろう
That's amazing.
すごいな
What do you have the most fun doing?
何してるときに一番楽しい?
Maybe when you're playing with friends.
友達と遊んでるときですかね
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
What do you play?
何して遊ぶの?
Eating food and watching movies.
ご飯食べたり、映画見たり
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
What kind of food do you like?
ご飯も何好きなの?
It's Yakiniku.
焼肉です
Yakiniku?
焼肉?
I see.
そっか
Then let's all go to Yakiniku.
じゃあみんなで焼肉行こうね
yes.
はい
please.
お願いします
Manatsu-chan, please stand up.
真夏ちゃんさ、立ってみて
yes.
はい
I like your great style.
すごいスタイルいいね
Are you on a diet?
ダイエットとかしてるの?
I haven't.
してないです
してないんだ
Are you eating properly?
ちゃんとご飯食べてる?
I'm eating.
食べてます
Her breasts are also quite big.
胸も結構大きいね
It's transparent underneath.
下には透けてるよ
Well then, could you show me the bottom?
じゃあさ、下に見せてくれる?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいです
My nose is completely white.
鼻真っ白だなぁ
It's such a beautiful body.
すごい綺麗な体だね
pure white.
真っ白
Looks like an idol.
アイドルみたいだね
Under your nose?
鼻の下に?
that's right.
そうです
You look great together.
すごい似合ってるね
cute.
かわいい
The bottom looks expensive.
高そうな下になる
How does it feel to be photographed?
撮られるのどう?
I'm nervous.
緊張してます
get nervous?
緊張する?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいです
I agree.
そうだね
Look back.
後ろ向いてみて
My butt is transparent.
尻透けてる
It's true.
本当だ
She's wearing really naughty pants.
これすごいエッチなパンツ履いてんじゃん
You're wearing really naughty pants.
めちゃくちゃエッチなパンツ履いてんね
Do you usually wear this?
これこんなの普段から履くの?
I'm wearing them.
履いてるんだ
This will get the man excited.
これは男テンション上がっちゃうでしょ
Well, just sit there for a while.
じゃあさ、そこちょっと座ってみて
It's really white.
ほんと真っ白だね
I can't catch fire.
火に焼けないんだ
Now, try opening your legs slowly.
じゃあさ、ゆっくり足開いてみて
I can't see it even though I can see it.
見えそうで見えない
It's so cute.
すごいかわいいね
Does it look embarrassing?
恥ずかしいと見れちゃう?
yes.
はい
Now, try being on all fours.
じゃあさ、四つん歯になってみて
Is this half erotic?
これ半足級にエロかな?
Below this.
この下に
You can see it.
見えちゃってるよね
Awesome, amazing.
すげえすげえ
Her butt is big and cute.
お尻大きくてかわいいんだよ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Well, look here.
そんまいこっち見て
Wow, this is naughty.
うわ、やらしいねこれ
Manatsu-chan, what kind of Tybee do you like?
真夏ちゃんどんなタイビー好きなの?
The naughty Tybee.
エッチのタイビーは
Thailand likes growth doctors.
タイは成長医が好きです
I like growth doctors.
成長医が好きなんだ
If my ass was this big, I'd want to fuck it from behind as hard as I can
こんなお尻大きかったらさ、 バックから思いっきりやりたくな
That's it.
っちゃ うね
Then come here again.
じゃあもう一回こっち来て
Well, Kuro-chan, from behind.
じゃあ黒ちゃんさ、 後ろからさ、
Would you like to touch these beautiful breasts?
この綺麗なおっぱい、 触ってみよっか
I want to touch it.
触りたい
Can I touch it?
触っていい?
Can you feel my breasts?
おっぱい感じる?
I feel it.
感じるんだ
soft.
柔らかい
It seems to have great elasticity.
すごい弾力ありそう
Dokuro-chan, touch me.
どう黒ちゃん、触って
It's insanely soft.
めちゃめちゃ柔らかい
Is there a mole in this naughty area?
これエッチのとこにほくらあるの?
That's right.
そうなんです
So let's move it a little bit.
じゃあちょっとずらしてみよっか
These are beautiful breasts.
綺麗なおっぱいだねこれ
Very beautiful nipples.
すごい綺麗な乳首
It was taken away.
取られちゃったね
Kuro-chan, please touch my nipples.
黒ちゃん、乳首触ってね
It's getting hard.
固くなってきた
How do you feel?
どんな気持ち?
It feels good.
気持ちいいです
Do you prefer having your breasts touched or licked?
おっぱい触られるのとさ、 舐められるのどっちが好き?
It's touched.
触られるのです
But I'll lick it.
でも舐めちゃうからね
copper?
どう?
Well, Kuro-chan, you're so cute.
じゃあ黒ちゃんさ、 この可愛いさ、
Look at your face.
お顔見て
So cute.
めっちゃ可愛い
Shall I pour you some?
ちょっと注してみよっか
Let's go.
いくよ
What does Kuro-chan taste like?
黒ちゃんどんな味する?
mint.
ミント
eat gum.
ガム食べる
It tastes like mint.
ミントの味するんだよ
Well then, let's take off your bra.
じゃあブラジャーちょっと取ってみよっか
What a beautiful shape.
すごい綺麗な形
amazing.
すごい
Only 3 people were licked, right?
3人しか舐められてもないんでしょ、
this.
これ
There's such a naughty nursing student.
こんなエッチな看護学生いるんだ
Kuro-chan, please touch my nipples.
黒ちゃん、ちょっと触ってみ、乳首
You're standing.
立ってるね
Just lick this nipple.
ちょっとこの乳首さ、 ペロペロ舐めちゃってよ
How about Manage-chan?
マネジちゃんどう?
It feels good.
気持ちいいね
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
You're sitting really well.
すごい座れちゃってるね
Both of them were so hot.
どっちもピンピンになっちゃったね
Is Kuro-chan delicious?
黒ちゃん美味しい?
Your face has become naughty.
顔がエッチになってきたね
So, Manatsu-chan, let's do this too.
じゃあ真夏ちゃん、 これもしちゃおうか
Midsummer.
真夏
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいね
Sit down.
座って
This is out.
出ちゃったよ、これ
Look, look, chin chin.
見て見て、チンチン
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいです
Take a closer look.
ちょっと近くで見てみて
Why don't you bring it?
持って寄ってみ?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいです
Just touch it with your finger.
ちょっと指で触ってみ
This is going to get really big from now on.
これ今からいっぱいでっかくなるよ
Wow, that's a naughty way of licking.
うわー、エッチな舐め方するね
I can't taste it.
味しないです
無味
What about Kuro-chan?
黒ちゃんどう?
licks me in a very disgusting way
すごい嫌らしい舐め方する
hey.
ね
Then eat slowly.
じゃあ ゆっくり食わえてみ
I ate a lot of it.
チンチン食べちゃったね
So erotic
すごいエロい
Yo.
よ
It makes such a naughty sound.
すごい エッチな音するしね
Is it big?
チンチン大きい?
It's big.
大きいです
Do you like big dicks?
大きいチンチン好き?
yes.
はい
So cute.
すごい可愛い
Kuro-chan, you're a big dick.
黒ちゃん、チンチンパンパンだね
Feels good.
気持ちいい
I'm talking here.
ここを喋ってる
My balls are getting used to it too.
玉もなれてみ
This is a really disgusting tongue.
すごい嫌らしいベロだね、これ
Take your time, starting from the bottom and taking every step.
下から先、一歩までゆっくりなれてみ
Eat yourself deep inside.
自分を奥まで食わえてみ
Is it painful there?
そこで苦しい?
You have a small mouth.
口小さいね
This girl has a head.
これちゃん、頭持ってさ
Even if it eats you deep inside.
奥まで食われても
painful?
苦しい?
It's painful.
苦しいね
You've already taken it deep inside.
もう奥まで奪ってるね
I'll take just a little more.
もうちょっとだけ奪うよ
It's painful.
苦しいぞ
First, try to take as many steps as possible.
先、一歩いっぱい奪ってみ
This is Gingin.
これちゃん、ギンギン
That's why it's so erotic.
それなんでエロいね
Well then, let's see this guy's pussy too.
じゃあさ、 この奴ちゃんもさ、 おまんこ見せてもらおうか
good?
いい?
Well then, let's go to bed.
じゃあ、ベッド行こうか
Take it off slowly.
ゆっくり脱いでこら
Your face is growing properly, too.
おケケも生えてるね、ちゃんと
hey.
ね
Your pussy is so small.
お まんこすっごいちっちゃいね
Just get up.
ちょっと起き上がってみ
Show me your face.
顔見せて
So, open it yourself.
それで、自分で開く
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
yes.
はい
You've seen it all.
全部見られちゃったね
Her pussy is so small.
おまんこすっごいちっちゃい
Have you ever been robbed like this?
こうやって奪られたことある?
Until now.
今まで
No.
ないです
There isn't.
ないんだ
Recently.
最近だね
Then get down on all fours and open your butt.
じゃあ四つん場合になってさ、 自分のお尻ガンって開いて
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
yes.
はい
Wow, this is so erotic.
わー、すっごいエロいこれ
My butthole is open too.
お尻の穴も開いてるよ
I'm tingling.
ヒクヒクしてる
Is your butt hole pink?
お尻の穴ピンクなの?
It's a really embarrassing fall.
すっごい恥ずかしいフォールしてる
How do you feel?
どんな気分?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
I'm stuck.
しくび立ってるよ
I stood up.
立っちゃいました
You stood up.
立っちゃったね
Be safe once again.
もう一回無事になって
Hold your legs and lie down.
足自分で抱えてさ、 寝っ転がって
This is embarrassing.
これ恥ずかしいね
Kuro-chan, take a look, come closer.
黒ちゃん、見てみ、近くに
It's a little damp.
ちょっと湿ってる
Is it damp?
湿ってる?
Look closer.
もっと近くで見て
What kind of smell?
どんな匂い?
Put it in?
入れに?
It doesn't smell.
匂いしない
匂いしないんだ
I might do a little bit.
少しだけするかも
What kind of smell?
どんな匂い?
The smell of body fluids?
体液の匂い?
Was it the smell of a girl's body fluids?
女の子の体液の匂いでした?
amazing.
すごい
The smell of a girl's body fluids.
女の子の体液の匂い
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいね
embarrassed
恥ずか
Yes.
しい
Keep your body straight.
体 を真っ直ぐに
Look.
見て
Kuro-chan.
黒ちゃん
Shall I lick it all from above?
上からさ、 全部舐めちゃおうか
yourself from above.
上から自分で
Next is the boobs.
次はおっぱい
She has a very naughty face.
すごいエッチな顔してる
I can feel my armpits.
脇感じちゃう
Aren't you embarrassed?
恥ずかしくない?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Next,
次は、
yes.
はい
Kuro-chan, please be more tongue-tied.
黒 ちゃん、もっとベロベロ
You look like you're about to say it.
言っちゃいそうな顔してるけど
Are you about to say it?
言っちゃいそうなの?
It feels so good.
気持ちよすぎる
Did it feel too good?
気持ちよすぎた?
Because I got licked on the chair.
椅子で舐められたから
It's soaked.
ビショビショだね
amazing.
すごい
Kuro-chan, spread it out and fill it.
黒ちゃん、広げていっぱい
It's soaked.
ビショビショだね
Very soaked.
すごいビショビショ
trout
マス
Hey, I like Cleatrice.
ちゃん さ、 クリートリス好きだ
Can Ben guess too?
ベンも当てちゃおうか
I'll guess this.
これ、当てるよ
Kuri-chan feels so good.
クリちゃん気持ちよすぎる
You're really nervous.
すごいビクビクしてるね
Oh, no.
あ、 ダメ
sensitive?
敏感?
Looks like Ben is guessing too.
ベンも当ててるっぽいけどね
It feels so good.
気持ちよすぎる
Feel good
気 持 ち よ す
Giru.
ぎ る
My feet feel so good.
足、すごく気持ちよすぎる
Ben guesses too.
ベンも当ててるよ
It feels so good here.
ここ、気持ちよすぎる
My feet are tingling.
足、ピリピリしてる
Mas-chan, you're so cute because you can feel it.
マスちゃん、感じてるから、すごいかわいいね
It's this way.
こっちだよ
I'll stand up in the room.
部屋で立ってやる
It's tingling here.
ここ、ピリピリしてる
I entered.
入った
I'm in, I'm in, I'm in, I'm in.
入った、入った、入った、入った
It's so erotic.
すごいエロい
Kuro-chan, please try picking up a mango.
クロちゃん、一旦マンゴー拾ってみて
Mango only once.
一度ばっかりのマンゴー
It's wetter than before.
さっきよりびしょびしょ
My legs are tingling too.
ヒクヒクしてるね、足もね
Don't you feel like you want to include it?
なんか、入れたくなってきたんじゃないの?
I feel like I want to put it in.
入れたい感じ
Shall we double it?
倍ぶりちゃおうか
It's thick, but will it fit?
太いけど、入るかな?
scared.
怖い
That's scary.
怖いね
Mas-chan, it's happening.
マスちゃん、なってるよ
Such a small mango.
こんなにちっちゃいマンゴーね
This is just barely.
ギリギリかな、これ
Put it in slowly, Kuro-chan.
ゆっくり入れてね、クロちゃん
Well then, I'll go slowly.
じゃあ、ゆっくり行くよ
Open your legs.
足、開いて
Which one will I go in?
どっちに入るのかな?
It hit me a while ago.
さっき、ぶつき刺さってるよ
Feels good.
気持ちいい
It's so erotic.
すごいエロいね
It stings.
ぶつ刺さってる
Amazing, it's absorbing.
すごい、吸い付いてる
Kuro-chan, aren't you tight?
ク ロちゃん、きついでしょ?
tight.
きつい
Put your feet on top like this.
足、こうやってさ、上にかかえる
Your hair is so erotic.
お毛毛がエロいね
Are you feeling better?
気持ちよくなってきたの?
It's really absorbing.
すごい吸い付いてるよ
The mango is crunchy.
マンゴーがパンパンだね
I'm bored.
いられちゃったね
Aren't they all going to open?
全部開いちゃうんじゃない?
How do you feel inside?
奥の気持ち?
Kuro-chan is tapping.
トントンってついてる、クロちゃん
I went in.
入っちゃった
All in, voila.
全部入って、ほら
This really hit me.
ぶつ刺さったよ、これ
I swallowed it.
飲み込んじゃったね
This is so erotic.
すごいエロしい、これ
Look, there's a hedge thread in there.
ほら、ヘッジな糸入ってる
So cute.
すごいかわいい
I'm going to be surprised.
もう、びっくり刺すよ
amazing.
すごい
I can fit that much already.
もう、そんな量入る
It's small, but it's all in there.
ちっちゃいように、全部入っちゃったね
Fall.
落ち
Put your finger in and see.
指入れて、ほら
It's a huge mess.
すごいぐちゃぐちゃしてる
There's a lot of tension, that.
すごい糸引いてるよ、あれ
Do your fingers feel good?
指、気持ちいい?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
What feels good, Mango?
どこが気持ちいいの、マンゴー?
G-spot?
Gスポット?
Where does it feel good?
どこが気持ちいいの?
Kuro-chan, I asked her to play with me where it felt good.
クロちゃん、気持ちいいとこ、いじってもらった
picture?
え?
All my fingers are in there.
指、全部入ってるから
Kumare.
く まれ
Where can I push it?
どこに振り押していい?
Will I fit in?
入るかな?
I was told to do this.
こうするって入ったね
Try the above sentiment.
上の気持ち入れをしてみて
good.
うまい
I'm good at it.
上手です
Kuro-chan makes such a cute face during Edge.
クロちゃん、エッジ中、すごいかわいい顔するんだね
It feels so good inside the mango.
気持ちいいんだ、マンゴーの中
It feels amazing.
すごい気持ちいい
It's a mess.
ぐちゃぐちゃだもんね
Try pulling it with your finger.
指で、パーって引いてみて
It feels so good.
気持ちよすぎる
You'll feel even better.
もっといっぱい気持ちよくなるよ
amazing.
すごい
It feels good here.
ここ気持ちいいんだね
Does it look like it's going to go away?
いっちゃいそう?
Would you like me to lick it all at once?
一気に舐めてもらおうか
copper?
どう?
This chin chin.
このチンチン
Take a good look.
よく見てみ
It's a bit small so it's full.
ちょっとちっちゃいからいっぱいだね
Gingin.
ぎんぎん
Your face is so colorful.
あなたちゃんの顔いろっきいね
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
There's a lot of dick from earlier.
さっきのチンチンいっぱいあるね
It's going to have a great edge.
すごいエッジになるね
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
It feels good.
気持ちいいんだね
It's really fun.
すごく楽しいね
Lick it at Cali.
カリのところ舐めて
Is it delicious?
チンチンおいしい?
Shall we lick each other?
舐め合いっこしようか
Take your chin chin and try to piece it.
チンチン持ってピースしてみて
Try peace.
ピースしてみて
Try peace
ピースしてみ
hand.
て
So cute.
すごい 可愛い
Your pussy is being licked.
マンコ舐められちゃってるね
It's big.
おっきいね
I wish I could lick it more.
もっといっぱい舐めていいな
Lick it a lot.
いっぱい舐めて
Her licking face is so cute.
すごい舐めてる顔も可愛いよ
That's amazing.
それすごいね
nervousness
緊張さ
Let me know.
せ る
I wanted to put it in.
入れたくなっちゃった
I'm going to put a big dick in it.
でっかいチンチン入れちゃう
It's amazing.
すごいパンパンだね
tight.
きつい
It's really tough.
すごいきついね
I said it looked like a tip.
先っぽいって言っちゃったけど
Your licking face is cute.
舐め顔可愛いんだね
tight?
きつい?
Did you switch this on?
これスイッチ入れたかい?
It felt so good.
めちゃくちゃ気持ち良くなった
Have Mana-chan follow you all the way.
マナちゃんの奥までついてもらう
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
It's stuck deep inside
奥まで刺さってるよ
all.
全部
Talking about cancellation.
中 止の話と
I have a lot of this.
これでいっぱいついて
It feels amazing.
すごい気持ちいい
Is Mana-chan tight?
マナちゃんきつい?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Let's move quickly now.
もう一気に動いておく
To the back.
奥まで
It might feel good.
気持ちいいかもしれない
It's facing the other way.
反対向けさ
I'll show you everything that's inside.
入ってるところいっぱい見せてもらう
Take it slow.
ゆっくりね
It's slow.
ゆっくりだよ
Because it's all included.
全部入ってるから
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Float your hips.
腰浮かしに
Try to follow Kuro-chan from underneath.
黒ちゃんの下から思いっきりついてみて
This feels so good.
これすごい気持ちいい
It feels good.
気持ちいいね
To the back.
奥まで
It feels good.
気持ちいいね
Kuro-chan, move as fast as you can.
黒ちゃん思いっきり早く動いて
It feels good, right?
気持ちいいでしょ
Shall I hit you from behind?
後ろから突こうか
So cute.
すごい可愛い
It feels good.
気持ちいいね
So cute.
すごい可愛い
Let's hit Kuro-chan as hard as we can.
黒ちゃん思いっきり突こうか
I'm going to rush into it.
突 いちゃう
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
She's such a pervert when she's so cute.
こんな 可愛いのすっごい変態
You've been there so many times.
すごいいっぱい行っちゃってるね
Does it hit deep?
奥まで当たる?
I hit a lot of them.
いっぱい当たってる
What about Kuro-chan's pussy?
黒ちゃんおまんこどう?
It's really absorbing.
すごい吸い付いてる
It'll stick to you.
吸い付いてくるね
Wow, it's in there.
すごいすごい入ってるよ
amazing.
すごい
Amazing Tara Tara.
すごいたらたら
It's amazing.
すごいし
That's amazing.
すごいね
Pussy.
おまんこ
Don
どん
Please feel at ease.
ど ん安心してね
Are you feeling better?
気持ちよくなってきた?
A lot of Kuro-chan came out.
黒ちゃんいっぱい出したね
Put your finger in.
指入れて
stomach
い
I was completely exposed.
っぱ い出されちゃった
He's so hot, with a face like this.
すごいイッチだね、こんな顔の
Please lick my dick.
いったちんちん舐めてもらえ
It felt so good.
気持ちよすぎました
It was so cute.
すっごい可愛かったよ
He looks so hot with a face like this.
こんな顔してすごいイッチなんだね
Kuro-chan, I want to do something naughty again.
黒ちゃんまたイッチなことしたいね
I want to.
したい
Manashi-chan, thank you for your concern.
まなしちゃん気をありがとうね
thank you very much.
ありがとうございました
bye bye.
バイバイ